Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- (Black notebook) Meeting of the American Bar Association: Commission on the Mentally Disabled (March 30, 1976) (Box 65)
- (Gray notebook) Meharry-Vanderbilt Center for Health Services Research and Health Policy Studies (Box 65)
- Report: Governor's Commission for Revision of the Mental Health Code of Illinois (1976) (Box 65)
- Mental Disability Law Report.er, volume 1, number 2 (September-october, 1976) (Box 65)
- Mental Disability Law Reporter, volume 1, number 3 (November-December, 1976) (Box 65)
- American Bar Association Commission on the Mentally Disabled (3 folders) (Box 65)
- Hobbs, Peabody Files (Box 66)
- Peabody Reflector (January-February, 1959) [2 copies] (Box 66)
- "Families Play to Grow," from Joseph P. Kennedy, Jr. Foundation, Washington, D.C. (3 unopened envelopes) (Box 66)
- Peabody College Correspondence - L (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - M (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - N (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - 0 (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence (Peabody Collection of Books on Children) (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Hobbs/Peabody/Kennedy Center Situation (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - Q,R (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - S (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - Stedman (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - Shriver (Box 66, Folder 18.00)
- Vanderbilt University - Hobbs' Courses (Box 67)
- Political Science 375, Seminar Papers and Correspondence (1980) (Box 67)
- Socio-Economic Political Science 375: Governments, Families, and Children (Spring, 1980) (Box 67)
- Sociology and Anthropology 375: Governments, Families, and Children (Spring, 1980) (Box 67)
- Textbook Order Forms (12/78) (Box 67)
- Freshman Seminar (Fall, 1979) (Box 67)
- Psychology 115: Final Examination (Box 67)
- Freshman Seminar (Fall, 1978) (Box 67)
- Freshman Seminar (Fall, 1977) (Box 67)
- Freshman Seminar (Fall, 1976) (Box 67)
- Freshman Seminar (Quizzes 5 and 6; Fall, 1978) (Box 67)
- Student Applications, Hobbs Seminar (Spring, 1977) (Box 67)
- Vanderbilt University - Advisees (Box 67)
- Freshman Advisees - Mr. Hobbs (Box 67)
- Baker, John (Box 67)
- Connors, Gerard J. (copy of dissertation) (Box 67)
- Connors, Gerard J. (copy of major area paper) (Box 67)
- Dodson, Tom (Box 67)
- Harkey, John (Box 67)
- Langford, Cynthia (Box 67)
- Reichenbach, Lisa (3 folders) (Box 67)
- Semrau, Lorne A. (2 folders) (Box 67)
- Smith, Terry (Box 67)
- Zambone-Ashley, Alana M. (Box 67)
- Zimmerman, Alice (2 folders) (Box 67)
- Ethics Group (Eric Engel) (Box 67)
- Graduate Faculty Council
- Vanderbilt Medical School
- Phi Beta Kappa
- Vanderbilt University Psychology Department
- Registrar's Report (Box 67)
- Sponsored Research
- Stahlman Chair in Medical Ethics (correspondence with Virgil LeQuire) (Box 67)
- Vanderbilt Student Government Association
- Nashville University Center (1978?) (Box 67)
- VIPPS, A History of [Also Center (CSFC) Program in Brief] (Box 67)
- Sigma Xi
- Peabody College Correspondence - A (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - B (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- feabody College Correspondence - C (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - D (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - E (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - F (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - G (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - H (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - I, J (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - J (Joint Commission on Mental Illness of Children) (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Peabody College Correspondence - K (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Kennedy Foundation (Kennedy International Symposium; Washington, D.C.; 10-16-71) (Box 68, Folder 18.00)
- Reel-to-Reel Tapes (Gifted Child Research) (Box 70)
- Speeches and Publications (Box 70)
- The Future of Children: Categories, Labels, and Their Consequences (Box 70)
- Speeches and Publications of Nicholas Hobbs (chronologically arranged) (Box 70)
- The House of the Educated Man - Peabody College Honors Assembly (5-18-66) (Box 70, Folder 20.06)
- (Book Review) Curing Unreason by Reason Sullivan (Hobbs, 2-2-56) (Box 70)
- Science and Ethical Behavior in American Psychologist (5-19-59) (Box 70, Folder 20.02)
- The Office of the Provost at Vanderbilt, AAUP Talk (11-13-67) (Box 70, Folder 19.02)
- The Divinity School and the University, Vanderbilt (9-21-67) (Box 70, Folder 19.01)
- Mental Health's Third Revolution (1968) (Box 70, Folder 20.09)
- The New American Scholar - Phi Beta Kappa Talk, Vanderbilt University (12-14-67) (Box 70, Folder 19.03)
- The Idea of a University (Talk to Vanderbilt Alumni, 6-8-68) (Box 70, Folder 19.04)
- Learning at Vanderbilt (11-1-68) (Box 70, Folder 19.05)
- Reeducation, Reality, and Community Responsibility (1968) (Box 70)
- "Ethics: Ethical Issues in the Social Sciences," reprinted from International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (Copy) United States Senate Committee on Government Operations Subcommittee on Government Research (Box 70)
- Presentation to the Vanderbilt University Assembly (3-4-69) (Box 70, Folder 19.06)
- The Snark May be a Boojum (9-10-69) (Box 70, Folder 19.07)
- Talk to Colloquim for Counselors, Vanderbilt (9-25-69) (Box 70, Folder 19.08)
- Report to Vanderbilt Senate and Faculties (12-4-69) (Box 70, Folder 19.09)
- Remarks Before the Vanderbilt University Senate (9-8-70) (Box 70, Folder 19.10)
- Remarks Before the Board of Trustees, Meharry Medical College (5-29-70) (Box 70, Folder 19.11)
- Remarks Before the Vanderbilt University Senate (9-8-70) (Box 70, Folder 19.12)
- On the Eve of Greatness: Dede Wallace Cente.r Dedication ( 11-13-70) (Box 70, Folder 19.14)
- Introduction of Nancy Hanks: Vanderbilt University Women's Symposium (11-19-70) (Box 70, Folder 19.15)
- Remarks to the Graduating Class, Peabody Dem School (5-29-71) The Vanderbilt Gazette, number 55 (February 12, 1971) (Box 70, Folder 19.17)
- Recognizing the Gifted Child, Top of the News (6-12-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.18)
- Talk to National Society for Autistic Children, Incorporated (6-24-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.19)
- The Teacher-Counselor, 25th Anniversary, Mental Health Act (6-28-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.20)
- "The Advancement of Teaching and Learning and the Education of Teachers at Vanderbilt," remarks before the University Senate (9-29-71) (Box 70)
- "The Human Rights of the Retarded," a paper presented to the Kennedy Foundation Scientific Symposium (10-16-71) (Box 70)
- "The Governance of Universities," remarks made at the Southern Newspaper Publishers Association Seminar (7-21-77) (Box 70)
- Introduction of Hain Ginott, Nashville (10-20-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.24)
- Remarks to South Carolina Mental Health Association (10-22-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.25)
- Preamble, Child Development Advisory Committee (10-26-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.26)
- Report on the Academic Programs to Vanderbilt University Board of Trust (11-5-71) (Box 70, Folder 19.27)
- "Introduction," seminar on the Future of Higher Education (Summer, 1971; Southern Newspaper Publishers Association) (Box 70)
- Statement to Faculty, Vanderbilt University School of Nursing (1-21-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.28)
- Notes on Talk to Faculty, College of Arts and Science (2-15-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.29)
- Remarks at Dale Farabee School Dedication, Lexington (4-9-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.30)
- "Remarks on the Academic Program," Alumni Reunion, Vanderbilt University (6-3-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.31)
- Notes for talk on Mental Health, Belleville, Illinois (10-19-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.32)
- Remarks to Vanderbilt University Alumni Association Board of Directors (10-28-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.33)
- Report on the Academic Programs of the University, Report to Board of Trust (11-3-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.34)
- "Faculty Tenure Today," report to Board of Trust (11-3-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.35)
- Remarks on the Academic Year Calendar, presented to the Faculty Senate (11-9-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.36)
- Knowledge-Linking Systems (11-9-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.37)
- Ethical Concerns in Psychology Counseling - Professional. Issues Seminar (12-9-72) (Box 70, Folder 19.38)
- Remarks at the Dedication of the Treehouse (Elkhart, Indiana; 2-15-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.39)
- Children in Institutions - Child Development Paper (3-5-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.40)
- Remarks of the Dedication of the Learning Resources Center, Meharry Medical College (4-6-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.41)
- "The Project on Classification of Exceptional Children," reprinted from Journal of Abnormal Child Psychology (1973) (Box 70)
- Remarks at Investiture Ceremonies, Vanderbilt University School of Nursing (5-25-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.42)
- A Natural History of an Idea: Project Re-ED (Kaufman book, 8-1-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.43)
- Notes for Orientation of New Members of the Faculties (8-31-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.45)
- Remarks to the Board of Trust (11-8-73) (Box 70, Folder 19.46)
- Opening Remarks for Meeting on Psychological Development of Children (Champaign-Urbana, Illinois; March 4-9, 1974) (Box 70, Folder 19.47)
- Statement for Vanderbilt University Board of Trust- Provost (5-3-74) (Box 70, Folder 19.48)
- Vanderbilt's Plan for Planning Round Table Presentation (5-9-74) (Box 70, Folder 19.49)
- Comments at Investiture Ceremony, Vanderbilt School of Nursing (5-15-74) (Box 70, Folder 19.50)
- Tenure and the Retention of Faculty, remarks at the Board of Trust (5-3-74) (Box 70, Folder 19.51)
- Notes for Orientation of New Members of the Faculties (Box 70, Folder 19.52)
- Notes for Talk to Council of Exceptional Children, Peabody College (1-27-75) (Box 70, Folder 19.53)
- Remarks at Conference on University Programs and Priorities, Montgomery Bell (February 21-22, 1975) (Box 70, Folder 19.54)
- An International Network of Child Development Research Centers (UNESCO Proposal; 12-23-74) (Box 70, Folder 19.55)
- Introduction of Bruce Mazlish, Vanderbilt University Centennial Symposium, "The Future of History" (4-2-75) (Box 70, Folder 19.56)
- Remarks at Dinner, 100th Anniversary Celebration of the Vanderbilt Divinity School (3-31-75) (Box 70, Folder 19.58)
- Introduction - Who Cares for American Children, NAS Committee Report (4-20-75) (Box 70, Folder 19.59)
- Project on Classification of Exceptional Children: Summary of Final Report (4-75) (Box 70, Folder 19.60)
- Outline for Talk to Educational Staff Seminar (Washington, 11-6-74) (Box 70, Folder 19.61)
- Children Today (July-August, 1975) (Box 70)
- "To Invent the Future, 1976 School Psychology; A Becoming Profession," paper presented at annual meeting of the Association of School Psychologists (3-25-76) (Box 70, Folder 19.62)
- Notes for Talk to Public Group (Tallehassee, Florida; 4-17-76) (Box 70, Folder 19.64)
- Notes on Talk to White House Conference on Handicapped (9-13-76) (Box 70, Folder 19.65)
- Governments - Families and Children (Chicago, 12-10-76) (Box 70, Folder 19.67)
- Ecology, Psychology and the Education of Exceptional Children (Quebec, 11-6-76) (Box 70, Folder 19.68)
- Parents as Experts (Box 70, Folder 19.69)
- International Medical News Service - Hobbs' Speech at APA Convention (Box 70, Folder 19.70)
- The Program of the Center for the Study of Families and Children (3-15-77) (Box 70, Folder 19.71)
- Family and School: A New Axis (Ortho Meeting - New York, 4-14-77) (Box 70, Folder 19.72)
- Comments on Paper by R.P. McDermott and Jeffrey Aron-Pirandello In Classroom Conference on Future of Special Education (Minneapolis, 4-26-77) (Box 70, Folder 19.74)
- Speeches and Publications; Old VIPPS Files (Box 71)
- Needed - A Knowledge Base for Public Policies Affecting Families and Children (St. Louis, Missouri, 5-5-77) (Box 71, Folder 19.73)
- Ethics and Values In Social Science Research - Diener and Crandall (book review), Chicago Press (5-16-77) (Box 71, Folder 19.75)
- Post Script: Ethical Issues in Social Science Research; Encyclopedia of Social Science (5-1-77) (Box 71, Folder 19.76)
- Ethical and Moral Issues in Behavior Control (Hobbs' Judy Mearigs paper, 9-1-77) (Box 71, Folder 19.77)
- Families and Foundations, presented to Ohio Foundations (10-13-77) (Box 71, Folder 19.78)
- (Booklet) Exceptional Teachers and Exceptional Learners - Instructional Strategies From Special Education: A Baker's (Box 71)
- Notes for Talk to Canadian Meeting on Learning Disabilities (Otawa, Canada; 10-25-77) "Ethical Issues in the Social Sciences," pages 267-278, in International Encyclopedia of Statistics, volume 1, 1978, (Kruskal and Tanur, editors) (Box 71, Folder 19.79)
- Children, Families and Mental Policy Making - Conference on Future Emphases on Research and Development in Children's Mental Health Services (1-78) (Box 71, Folder 19.81)
- Children, Families, and Public Policies - Centennial Club (1-25-78) (Box 71, Folder 19.82)
- Classification Options .... Exceptional Children (1978) Ethics of Behavior Control, pages 23-38, in Mearig, J.S. and Associates (editors), Working for Children: Ethical Issues Beyond Professional Guidelines (1978) (Box 71, Folder 19.83)
- An Ecologically-Oriented, Service-Based Classification System: 11th Annual Gatlinburg Conference on Research in Mental Retardation (3/8-10/78) (Box 71, Folder 19.84)
- An Ecologically-Oriented, Service-Based Classification System for the Employment of Handicapped Adolescents (Montreal, 4-24-78), International Association Workers (Box 71, Folder 19.85)
- Where is Emotional Disturbance? The Round Table (6-1-78) "Can Public Policy Strengthen Families?" (draft for APA paper, 8-21-79) (Box 71, Folder 19.89)
- "The Families and Communities of Children in Residential Care," Jerusalem, Isreal (September 10-14, 1978) Youth Aliyah (Box 71, Folder 19.92)
- Talk to DAR on October 12, 1978 (same as for Centennial Club) (Box 71, Folder 19.93)
- Foreward for Campbell Loughmiller's book (10-25-78) (Box 71, Folder 19.95)
- Project Re-ED or "Re-education Treatment techniques.. .," paper given in Winston-Salem on November 3-4, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 19.96)
- "Knowledge Transfer and the Policy Process," a paper presented to the Child Abuse, Cultural Roots and Policy Options Conference (University of Pennsylvania, 11-20-78) (Box 71)
- "Child Abuse: An Agenda for Action," edited by G. Gerbner, C.J. Ross, and E. Zigler (1980) (Box 71)
- Re-ED in North Carolina, by Algund Hermann and Nicholas Hobbs (12-78) (Box 71, Folder 20.01)
- Linking Knowledge to Action: A Strategy for Citizen's Advisory Groups, paper given (Louisville, Kentucky; 12-5-78) (Box 71, Folder 19.99)
- Handouts for Select Committee for the Study of Children's Services, Tennessee State Legislature (January 5-6, 1979) (Box 71, Folder 20.00)
- "About Education: Special Education in Regular Classes," by Gene I. Maeroff, New York Times (12-11-79) (Box 71)
- Papers on Research About Learning: Exceptional Teaching for Exceptional Learning, a report to the Ford Foundation by Nicholas Hobbs and Others (5-79) (Box 71)
- "Children, Families, and Public Policies," by Nicholas Hobbs (5-10-79) (Box 71)
- Families, Schools, and Communities: An Ecosystem for Children, pages 192-202, in Families and Communities as Educators; H.J. Leichter, editor (July;-1979) -Interview with Nicholas Hobbs in The Directive Teacher by Tom Stephens, volume 1, number 4 (Spring, 1979) (Box 71, Folder 20.02)
- Dust jacket quotation for Before the Best Interests of the Child by J. Goldstein, Anna Freud and A. Solnit (Box 71)
- Foreward for Reuven Feuerstein's book, Instrumental Enrichment (8-27-79) (Box 71)
- Can Public Policy Strengthen Families? (notes for APA Symposium, 9-4-79) (Box 71)
- Round Table Talk: The Professor and the Student or the Art of Getting Students Into Trouble (10-4-79) (Box 71)
- Foreward for Laura Knox's book (1-22-80) (Box 71)
- Article by Hobbs and Shayne in the Spring, 1980 issue of Change (Box 71)
- Vanderbilt Institute for Public Policy Studies (Box 71, Folder 16.00)
- General Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 16.01)
- Sivley Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 16.02)
- VIPPS Planning (Box 71, Folder 16.021)
- Gazette Statement Establishing VIPPS (Box 71, Folder 16.03)
- Drafts of VIPPS Statement (Box 71, Folder 16.031)
- Godwin, Sperduto, Womer paper on VIPPS (Box 71, Folder 16.032)
- Knauss Memo to the Chancellor (3-3-75) (Box 71, Folder 16.04)
- Booklets, pamphlets, leaflets (Box 71, Folder 16.05)
- Prospective Personnel (Box 71, Folder 16.06)
- Budget (Box 71, Folder 16.07)
- Search Committee for Director of VIPPS (Box 71, Folder 16.08)
- Correspondence; re: Director of VIPPS (Box 71, Folder 16.081)
- VIPPS Director Candidate: Louis H. Masotti (Box 71, Folder 16.0811)
- VIPPS Director Candidate: Erwin C. Hargrove (Box 71, Folder 16.0812)
- VIPPS Director Candidate: Steven Ebbin (Box 71, Folder 16.0813)
- VIPPS Director Candidate: Jay Demerath, III (Box 71, Folder 16.0814)
- VIPPS Director Candidate: John C. Weicher (Box 71, Folder 16.0815)
- Advisory Committee for VIPPS (Box 71, Folder 16.09)
- VIPPS Executive Committee Meetings (Box 71, Folder 16.091)
- Library (Box 71, Folder 16.10)
- Program Centers (Box 71, Folder 16.11)
- Possible Program Centers (Box 71, Folder 16.111)
- Meharry-Vanderbilt Health Center Meharry-Vanderbilt Grant (1975) Addendum to the Meharry-Vanderbilt Center for Health Services Research and Policy Studies Grant (HS 01969-01) (Box 71, Folder 16.112)
- Veterans Administration Hospital Cooperation Proposal (Box 71, Folder 16.1121)
- Environment and Energy Center (Box 71, Folder 16.113)
- Urban and Regional Development Center Presidents' Commission (Box 71, Folder 16.114)
- Commission on the Mentally Disabled; Old VIPPS (Sivley) (Box 72)
- Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education
- Gazette Announcement
- Gazette - Vanderbilt (Box 72)
- Governments, Families and Children (Nicholas Hobbs) (Box 72)
- Gray Panthers
- Habitat National Center
- Health Communications Seminar
- Health Facilities Commission
- Health Insurance Institute
- Hobbs' Itinerary (Box 72)
- Indirect Cost Rates
- Sidney Johnson
- Robin Huws Jones
- Joyce Laben (Nursing) (Box 72)
- Judi Lachman
- Lachman Paper (VIPPS) (Box 72)
- Law Enforcement Assistance Administration
- Legal Aid Society
- Legislative Proposals
- Maureen Mahoney
- Mailings Lists
- Nashville Contacts
- Microfiche - Legislative Status Reports (Box 72)
- Nashville Human Rights Forum
- Nursing
- Osterrieth
- Program Center - Urban and Regional Development (Box 72)
- Proposal Solicitations
- Public Relations
- Public Safety Conferences
- Public Sector Economics and Policy Process
- Revenue Sharing
- Rowley General Memo (6-6-75) (Box 72)
- Schedules
- Richard D. Sivley (Box 72)
- Daniel Socolow
- Solar Energy Conference
- Supplemental Security Income
- Swine Flu Proposal
- Technical Center Contract
- Tennessee Preparatory School
- Title I Grants - General Information (Box 72)
- Title IV - B (Box 72)
- United Southeastern Tribes
- Census Information (1980) (Box 72)
- Census
- Contacts - Individuals (Box 72)
- David Dunlop
- Past Personnel (Sivley, Richard) (Box 72)
- Correspondence - Dan Costello (Box 72)
- Present Personnel (Lachman, Judith) (Box 72)
- Judi Lachman
- Past Personnel (Costello, Daniel) (Box 72)
- Institute for Public Policy Guest List
- Personnel (Pascal, Chris) (Box 72)
- Urban Center (VIPPS) (Box 72)
- Urban Observatory
- Urban and Regional Development Center (final report) (Box 72)
- (URDC) Health Policy Seminar (Spring, 1975; Zubkoff) (Box 72)
- Urban and Regional Development Center (Seminars, 1974-1975) (Box 72)
- Vickrey, Barry - Law (Box 72)
- Juvenile Justice Standards; Commission on the Mentally Disabled; Old VIPPS (Sivley) (Box 73)
- Juvenile Justice Standards Project (3 folders) (Box 73, Folder 17.801)
- Commission on the Mentally Disabled (Box 73, Folder 17.802)
- To File - VIPPS (Box 73)
- Advisory Committee - Vipps (Box 73)
- Afro-American Religions (Proposed Center) (Box 73)
- Wendy Allred
- American Health Profiles, Incorporated (Box 73)
- Brown, Anne (Box 73)
- Children's Hospital - VIPPS (Box 73)
- Copier
- Correspondence - Rick Sivley (Box 73)
- Ads for Courses
- Costello, Daniel E. (Box 73)
- Director - VIPPS (Box 73)
- Divinity School
- Duplicating
- (ECS) Education Commission of the State (Box 73)
- Economic Development Administration
- Economics of Crime (Lachman) (Box 73)
- Executive Coordinating Committee - VIPPS (Box 73)
- Family Impact Seminar
- Faculty Senate
- Forensics
- Publication draft of Reeducating Troubled and Troubling Children and Youth by Nicholas Hobbs (11-25-80, revision copy) (Box 74)
- Dedication: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Outline: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Acknowledgements: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Title Page: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Foreward to Pre-publication Edition: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Contributors: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Contents: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Preface: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Chapter 1: Re-ED Book (Box 74)
- Chapter 2 - (6 folders: 5 labeled simply Chapter 2, 1 labeled "Re-ED Book-- Chapter 2, 'What Re-ED Programs are Like'"; 5-26-80) (Box 74)
- Re-ED Chapter 5: The Process of Reeducation, Ecological Strategies (4 folders) New 5, Consultants (Box 75)
- Re-ED Chapter 6: Ecological Assessment and Enablement Planning (7 folders) (Box 75)
- Re-ED Chapter 6: The Liaison Function (3 folders) Chapter 7 (3 folders) (Box 75)
- Re-ED Chapter 7: The Process of Re-Education: Psychological and Educational Strategies (3 folders) Re-ED Chapter 8 (4 folders) (Box 75)
- Chapter 9: Enterprise (Box 76)
- Chapter 9: Learning to Learn (5 folders) (Box 76)
- Chapter 9 (old copy) (Box 76)
- Chapter 10: Learning to Behave (5 folders) (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Re-ED Panel of Visitors (1980; 1981) (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Panel of Visitors - Eli Bower (July 28-29, 1980) (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Panel of Visitors -Wayne Holtzman (July 28-29, 1980) (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Panel of Visitors - Reg Lourie (July 28-29, 1980) (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Panel of Visitors - Dr. Chuck Strother (7-29-80) (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Panel of Visitors - Group Discussion (Hobbs, holtzman (Box 76)
- Lourie, Strother, Bower; 7-29-80) Epilogue (old) (Box 76)
- Re-ED References (Box 76)
- Epilogue: Panel of Visitors' Report (6-26-81; revision) (Box 76)
- Re-ED Epilogue: An Evaluation of Project Re-ED, report of a Panel of Visitors (Box 76)
- Re-ED Panel of Visitors Project: Epilogue (Box 76)
- Appendix I
- Evaluation
- Re-ED Book: Chapter 3 - The Teacher Counselor Teacher-Counselor Autobiographies (Box 77)
- Chapter 3
- Chapter 3 Questionnaires Hutton, Roy - Re-ED Book Project; Chapter 3 (Summer, 1978) (Box 77)
- Chapter 3 (5 folders) (Box 77)
- Chapter 4: Re-ED Book - Children and Adolescents Served (5 folders) (Box 77)
- (Videocassette in box) "Parents of Disturbed Children" [Sony KC - 30 - 28'38"] (Box 78)
- Girls' Adventure Trails (Box 78, Folder 17.75)
- Re-ED (General Information, A-o) (Box 78, Folder 18.021)
- Re-ED (General Information, P-Z) (Box 78, Folder 18.021)
- "Helping Disturbed Children and Their Families: Project Re-ED, Twenty Years Later," by Nicholas Hobbs (draft, 10-1-78) (Box 78)
- "Helping Disturbed Children and Their Families: Project Re-ED, Twenty Years Later" (APA meeting, Toronto, 8-31-78) (Box 78, Folder 19.91)
- Ecological Assessment and Enablement Plan (7-27-78) - Peabody College (Second National Invitation Liaison Conference) (Box 78, Folder 19.90)
- Helping Disturbed Children: Psychological and Ecological Strategies, II: Project Re-ED, Twenty Years Later (original manuscript and copy) (Box 78)
- Cover letter from Nicholas Hobbs concerning pre-publication of Project Re-ED (3-1-79) Re-ED red book (3-1-79) (Box 78)
- Re-ED paper (Box 78)
- Helping _Disturbed children: Psychological and Ecological Strategies, II; Project Re-ED, Twenty Years Later (6-79) (Box 78)